I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'VE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE.
THIS IS SO GOOD...
SO GOOD FOR MONICA.
( bell dings )
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
TIME'S UP. MY TURN.
THAT WAS A HALF AN HOUR?
IT'S YOUR TIMER.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, I
DON'T LIKE TO
BRAG ABOUT IT
BUT I GIVE, LIKE,
THE BEST MASSAGES.
ALL RIGHT. THEN
MASSAGE ME UP RIGHT NICE.
AH! AH! AH!
IT'S SO GOOD, ISN'T IT?
IT'S SO GOOD, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'VE DONE TO DESERVE IT.
OH, GOD.
SAY GOOD-BYE TO SORE MUSCLES.
GOOD-BYE, MUSCLES.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
I'M TELLING YOU,
SHE GIVES THE WORST
MASSAGES EVER, OKAY?
IT WAS LIKE SHE
WAS TORTURING ME
FOR INFORMATION
AND I WANTED
TO GIVE IT UP.
I JUST... I DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT IT WAS.
LOOK, CHANDLER, IF IT
REALLY HURTS THAT BAD
YOU SHOULD JUST TELL HER.
LOOK. FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M IN A REAL
RELATIONSHIP, OKAY?
I'M NOT GOING
TO SCREW THAT UP
BY, YOU KNOW,
TELLING THE TRUTH.
HEY.
WHOA, DUDE, LOOK OUT.
DUDE, YOU ALMOST
CRUSHED MY HAT.
I'M-I'M SORRY.
AND THE BUNNY
GOT AWAY.
THIS WOULD BE THE PLACE
WHERE YOU EXPLAIN THE HAT.
OH, YEAH.
THERE'S THIS PLAY, RIGHT?
AND I'M UP FOR THE PART
OF THIS REAL COOL, LIKE,
SUAVE, INTERNATIONAL GUY--
A REAL CLOTHESHORSE.
SO I FIGURE EVERYONE
AT THE AUDITION
IS GOING TO BE WEARING
THIS KIND OF, YOU KNOW
ULTRA-HIP,
HIGH FASHION STUFF.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE THEM
ALL DISAPPEAR.
YEAH. LIKE YOU COULD
FIND SOMETHING
AS SOPHISTICATED AS THIS.
( derisive chuckle )
DONE.
JOEY, IF YOU WANT TO LOOK GOOD
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
COME DOWN TO THE STORE.
I'LL HELP YOU OUT.
OH, GREAT. THANKS, RACH.
SURE.
GOD, PLEASE TAKE THOSE OFF.
ALL RIGHT.
Ross:
HEY, PHEEBS,
HOW'S IT GOING?
HEY.
WELL, ONLY OKAY
'CAUSE I JUST
GOT BACK FROM
THE HOSPITAL.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE. I'M OKAY,
BUT MY GRANDMA SORT OF DIED.
Joey:
OH, PHEEBS, SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, SHE
HAD A REALLY
INCREDIBLE LIFE
AND IT'S NOT LIKE I'M
NEVER GOING TO SEE
HER AGAIN, YOU KNOW.
SHE'S GOING TO VISIT.
WELL, MAYBE...
MAYBE SHE'S
WITH US RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HER FIRST DAY ON
A NEW SPIRITUAL PLANE
AND SHE'S GOING TO COME
TO THE COFFEEHOUSE.
YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS, I JUST SAW
TWO PEOPLE HAVING SEX
IN A CAR RIGHT OUTSIDE.
UH, PHEEBS' GRANDMOTHER
JUST DIED.
OH. OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S KIND OF COOL,
'CAUSE IT'S, LIKE...
YOU KNOW, ONE LIFE ENDS
AND ANOTHER BEGINS.
NOT THE WAY THEY'RE DOING IT.
WHAT... WHAT HAPPENED?
I'M SORRY.
HOW DID SHE DIE?
WELL, OKAY.
WE WERE IN
THE MARKET
AND SHE BENT DOWN
TO GET SOME YOGURT
AND SHE JUST NEVER
CAME BACK UP AGAIN.
PHEEBS, I'M SO SORRY.
IT WAS REALLY SWEET.
THE LAST THING
SHE SAID TO ME
WAS, "OKAY, DEAR,
YOU GO GET THE EGGS
"AND I'M GOING
TO GET THE YOGURT
AND WE'LL MEET AT
THE CHECKOUT COUNTER."
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE WILL MEET AT THE
CHECKOUT COUNTER.
JOEY, YOU KNOW THAT
SINCE YOU'RE RETURNING
ALL THIS STUFF
AFTER THE AUDITION
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO WEAR UNDERWEAR.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, YOU
BETTER SHOW ME SOME
OF THAT, TOO, THEN.
OKAY. IT'S
MISSING SOMETHING.
OH, I KNOW.
UM, OKAY.
REALLY? A PURSE?
IT'S NOT A PURSE.
IT'S A SHOULDER BAG.
LOOKS LIKE
A WOMAN'S PURSE.
NO, JOEY.
LOOK, TRUST ME.
I'M TELLING YOU,
ALL OF THE MEN
ARE CARRYING THEM
IN THE SPRING CATALOG.
LOOK. SEE? LOOK.
MEN... CARRYING THE BAG.
SEE? LOOK.
WOMEN CARRYING THE BAG.
BUT IT IS ODD
HOW A WOMAN'S PURSE
LOOKS SO GOOD
ON ME, A MAN.
EXACTLY.
UNISEX.
MAYBE YOU NEED SEX.
I HAD SEX
A COUPLE DAYS AGO.
NO, NO, JOEY.
"U-N-I" SEX.
WELL, I AIN'T GONNA
SAY "NO" TO THAT.
Ursula:
WHO IS IT?
IT'S PHOEBE.
OH, GREAT.
OH, YOU.
UM, WHAT'S UP?
UM, WELL, I... SORT
OF HAVE SOME BAD NEWS.
CAN I COME IN?
UM, YEAH. NO, THANKS.
UM... WELL... UM...
GRANDMA DIED TODAY.
WOW.
DIDN'T SHE DIE, LIKE,
FIVE YEARS AGO?
NO, SHE JUST DIED TODAY.
UM, OKAY.
WE'RE HAVING
A MEMORIAL SERVICE TOMORROW.
OKAY. I KNOW I WENT
TO THAT ALREADY.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
THEN WHO'S BEEN
DEAD FOR FIVE YEARS?
WELL, LOTS OF PEOPLE.
LOOK. ARE
YOU COMING
TO THE MEMORIAL
SERVICE OR NOT?
UM, NO.
SEE, I ALREADY
THOUGHT
SHE WAS DEAD
SO I'VE KIND OF MADE
MY PEACE WITH IT.
AND PLUS, I'M GOING
TO A CONCERT TOMORROW, SO...
I'D INVITE YOU
BUT I ONLY HAVE
TWO TICKETS LEFT.
FINE.
OKAY. ENJOY
YOUR CONCERT.
THANKS. ENJOY
YOUR FUNERAL.
HEY.
WOW. YOU LOOK JUST LIKE
YOUR SON, MRS. TRIBBIANI.
WHAT?
ARE YOU REFERRING
TO MY MAN'S BAG?
AT FIRST I THOUGHT
IT JUST LOOKED GOOD
BUT IT'S PRACTICAL, TOO.
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S GOT COMPARTMENTS
FOR ALL YOUR STUFF--
YOUR WALLET, YOUR KEYS,
YOUR ADDRESS BOOK...
YOUR MAKEUP.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING WITH THE BAG?
YOUR AUDITION'S
NOT TILL TOMORROW.
YEAH, BUT SANDWICH TIME
IS RIGHT NOW.
JOEY, YOU KNOW YOU GET
ANY MUSTARD ON THAT BAG
YOU CAN'T RETURN IT.
WHY WOULD I RETURN THIS?
I LOVE THIS BAG.
ALL RIGHT.
THEN YOU OWE ME $350.
Joey:
FINE.
DO YOU TAKE VASA
OR MOOSTERCARD?
JOEY...
ALL RIGHT. RELAX.
LOOK. I'LL PAY YOU
WITH THE MONEY
FROM THE ACTING JOB
I AM DEFINITELY GOING TO GET
THANKS TO YOU.
WHAT'S THE PART? AUNTIE MAME?
DON'T LISTEN TO THEM.
I THINK IT'S SEXY.
"YOU AND I" SEXY?
OH, HELLO, MRS. PINELLO.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING.
OKAY. HERE'S
YOUR 3-D GLASSES.
AND REVEREND PONG WILL TELL YOU
WHEN TO PUT THEM ON.
HI, SWEETIE.
HOW ARE YOU
HOLDING UP?
FINE.
HEY, PHEEBS.
I'M SO SORRY.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
MY GRANDMA HAD
THE EXACT SAME BAG.
HERE. I BROUGHT YOU
SOME FLOWERS.
OH, THANKS.
YEAH. PULLING FLOWERS
OUT OF IT
MAKES THE BAG LOOK
A LOT MORE MASCULINE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
EXCUSE ME. IS THIS
THE MEMORIAL?
YEAH. WELCOME.
HELLO.
HERE'S YOUR
3-D GLASSES.
OH... ALL RIGHT.
SO, HOW DID YOU KNOW FRANCES?
WELL, ACTUALLY...
I HADN'T SEEN HER
FOR YEARS, BUT, UM...
WELL, I WAS PRETTY TIGHT
WITH HER AND HER DAUGHTER.
REALLY? WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
FRANK BUFFAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT? STRIKE THAT.
MY NAME... ACTUALLY, IS-IS JOE.
UM...
JOE... UH, HILL.
YOU'RE FRANK BUFFAY?
( whispering ):
SHH! NO!
JOE HILL!
BUT YOU JUST SAID...
YOU KNOW WHAT? I GOT TO GO
AND THANK YOU
SO MUCH FOR COMING.
BUT...
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
Monica:
WHAT, HONEY?
THAT WAS MY DAD.
OH, MY GOD.
HEY, YOU GUYS, CHECK
IT OUT, CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S LIKE IT'S
COMING RIGHT AT ME.
DID YOU
CATCH HIM?
UH-HUH.
WHAT DID
HE SAY?
HE SAID, "NICE TO
MEET YOU, GLENDA."
WELL, OBVIOUSLY, I COULDN'T
GIVE HIM MY REAL NAME.
WHY? WHY NOT?
YOU SAW THE WAY
HE RAN OUT OF HERE.
YOU THINK HE'D STICK AROUND
AND TALK TO THE DAUGHTER
HE ABANDONED?
WHAT DID YOU
SAY TO HIM?
I TOLD HIM I WAS THE EXECUTOR
PERSON OF FRANCES'S WILL
AND THAT I NEEDED
TO TALK TO HIM
SO I'M GOING TO MEET HIM
AT THE COFFEEHOUSE LATER.
( funeral music playing )
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I JUST CAN'T
THINK ABOUT THAT NOW.
I-I JUST WANT
TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO MY GRANDMA.
OKAY. LET'S GO
SAY GOOD-BYE.
HEY.
I'M OFF
TO MY AUDITION.
HOW DO I LOOK?
I THINK YOU LOOK GREAT.
JOEY, THAT BAG IS GOING
TO GET YOU THAT PART.
AND A DATE
WITH A MAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAKE FUN ALL YOU WANT.
THIS IS A GREAT BAG, OKAY?
AND IT'S AS HANDY
AS IT IS BECOMING.
NOW, JUST BECAUSE
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND SOMETHING
DOESN'T MAKE IT WRONG,
ALL RIGHT?
SO, FROM NOW ON,
YOU GUYS ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO GET USED TO THE FACT
THAT JOEY COMES WITH A BAG.
I BETTER GO, TOO. I
GOT TO GO MEET MY DAD.
PHEEBS, ARE YOU
GOING TO TELL
HIM WHO YOU ARE?
NO, NOT AT FIRST,
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO FREAK HIM OUT.
BUT AREN'T YOU PISSED
AT HIM?
I MEAN, THIS GUY ABANDONED YOU.
I GOT TO TELL YOU,
IF IT WERE ME
THIS GUY WOULD BE
IN SOME SERIOUS PHYSICAL DANGER.
I-I-I'D WALK IN THERE...
I'D BE, LIKE, "YO, DAD!
YOU AND ME OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW!"
I KIND OF SCARED MYSELF.
WELL, AT LEAST YOU
SCARED SOMEONE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
YOU'D THINK I'D BE ANGRY.
I MEAN, YOU'D THINK
I'D WANT TO RIP HIS
TINY LITTLE HEAD OFF.
FORTUNATELY, I'M PAST IT, SO...
PHOEBE, YOU DO SEEM
A LITTLE TENSE.
HERE. LET ME HELP YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
GET OFF!
OW! OH, STOP IT!
WHY? WHY ARE YOU
DOING THAT TO ME?!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
AS A MASSEUSE AND A HUMAN
I'M BEGGING YOU,
NEVER DO THAT TO ANYONE.
I GIVE GOOD MASSAGES.
( scoffs )
I USED TO GIVE THEM
TO RACHEL ALL THE TIME
BEFORE SHE GOT ALLERGIC.
AND CHANDLER...
HE LOVES THEM. WATCH.
HE DOES NOT LIKE IT.
HE HATES IT.
HE'S IN PAIN.
NO, HE'S NOT.
YES, HE IS.
WHAT?
I'M SORRY, BUT... OW! OW! OW!
HAVE YOU BEEN
LYING TO ME?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D DO THAT.
MAYBE HE JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO HURT YOUR FEELINGS.
BUT THE MINUTE WE START
TO LIE TO EACH OTHER...
AND BY "WE"
I MEAN SOCIETY...
ANY TIME YOU'RE
READY, JOEY.
"WELL, YOU MUST BE NEW HERE.
MAYBE WE GET A TABLE
AND I BUY YOU A DRINK."
I'M SORRY.
COULD YOU... COULD YOU TRY IT
WITHOUT THE PURSE?
YEAH. SURE.
"WELL, YOU MUST
BE NEW HERE.
"MAYBE WE SIT...
I'M SORRY.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
SURE. WHAT?
WELL, FIRST, IT'S NOT A PURSE.
OKAY. ANY TIME.
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE THINKING
IT'S A WOMAN'S BAG, IT'S NOT.
IT'S A MAN'S BAG.
OKAY, AND GO.
LET ME SHOW
YOU THE CATALOG.
LOOK. SEE? HUH?
IT'S THE
LATEST THING.
EVERYONE'S
GOT ONE:
MEN, WOMEN,
CHILDREN.
EVERYONE'S
CARRYING THEM.
DO YOU SELL THESE BAGS?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THESE BABIES SELL THEMSELVES.
OKAY. THANK YOU.
THAT WAS GREAT.
YEAH, BUT I DIDN'T EVEN READ
ANYTHING.
I THINK WE'VE SEEN ENOUGH.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT. I'LL SEE YOU.
WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT.
HEY, IS RACHEL HERE?
NO.
LISTEN, I JUST WANTED
TO APOLOGIZE
ABOUT THIS AFTERNOON
AND THE WHOLE MASSAGE
THING, YOU KNOW?
I-I REALLY LIKE THEM.
PLEASE, STOP.
WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE HONEST
WITH EACH OTHER.
I JUST WISH
YOU COULD TELL ME.
JUST SAY IT:
"I DON'T LIKE
YOUR MASSAGES."
I DON'T LIKE
YOUR MASSAGES.
( voice breaking ):
SEE? IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
OKAY, BUT NOW, SEE?
YOU'RE CRYING.
I'M NOT CRYING
ABOUT THAT.
I'M CRYING
ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED AT WORK.
WHAT?
MY BOYFRIEND SAID HE
DIDN'T LIKE MY MASSAGES!
IT'S OKAY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
THE BEST AT EVERYTHING.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU DON'T KNOW ME AT ALL!
OKAY. YOU GIVE THE WORST
MASSAGES IN THE WORLD.
I'M CRYING HERE!
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
HEAR ME OUT, OKAY?
YOU GIVE THE BEST
BAD MASSAGES, OKAY?
IF ANYBODY WAS LOOKING
FOR THE BEST BAD MASSAGE
AND THEY WERE THINKING
TO THEMSELVES
"WHO'S THE BEST AT THAT?"
THEY'D HAVE TO GO TO YOU.
HUH.
SO, YOU'RE SAYING
THAT, LIKE, UM...
IF THERE WAS AN AWARD
FOR THE BEST BAD MASSAGE...
WELL, WHO WOULD GET THAT?
OH, IT WOULD BE YOU.
YOU, MONICA
AND YOU'D GET
ALL THE VOTES.
SO, MAYBE THEY COULD, UM,
CALL THE AWARD "THE MONICA"?
ABSOLUTELY.
OKAY.
I SUCK.
YEAH.
THANK YOU FOR MEETING WITH ME.
THANK YOU. ALL RIGHT.
COME SIT.
SIT.
SIT!
UM, ALL RIGHTY.
UM, BEFORE WE GET
STARTED, I'D JUST...
I NEED YOU TO STATE
FOR THE, YOU KNOW,
OFFICIAL RECORD
THAT YOU ARE, IN FACT,
FRANK BUFFAY.
OH, YES. YES, YES, I AM. MM-HMM.
OKAY.
SO...
WHAT DID FRANCES LEAVE ME?
HUH?
THAT'S WHY YOU WANTED
ME TO COME, RIGHT?
OH, YES.
YES. YEAH. NO, SHE DID.
SHE LEFT YOU, UM...
THIS LIPSTICK.
OH... HUH.
THAT'S...
OH, IT'S USED.
UH, COOL.
OKAY. I HAVE JUST
A FEW QUESTIONS TO ASK
SO I'M GOING TO GET
OUT MY OFFICIAL FORMS.
OKAY. SO, QUESTION ONE:
YOU WERE MARRIED
TO FRANCES'S DAUGHTER, LILY.
IS THAT CORRECT?
YES. YES, I WAS.
OKAY. UM, QUESTION TWO:
UM, "DID THAT MARRIAGE END,
A: HAPPILY, B: MEDIUM
OR C: IN THE TOTAL ABANDONMENT
OF HER AND HER TWO CHILDREN?"
IT REALLY SAYS THAT?
YEAH. SEE?
WELL, I GUESS
THAT I WOULD
HAVE TO SAY "C."
HMM. OKAY.
TOTAL ABANDONMENT, MM-HMM.
OKAY. "REASONS
FOR ABANDONMENT."
UM, "A: TOP SECRET
GOVERNMENT WORK, B: AMNESIA
OR C: YOU'RE JUST A SELFISH,
IRRESPONSIBLE, BAD, BAD MAN?"
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
THINK I WANT THE
LIPSTICK THAT MUCH
BUT, UH... OH, WOULD
YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND, UM, WOULD YOU GIVE
HER DAUGHTER LILY
THAT, PLEASE?
WHAT?
LILY. WHEN YOU
SEE LILY
WOULD YOU GIVE
HER THAT NOTE
BECAUSE I WANTED
TO TALK TO HER
AT THE MEMORIAL.
WELL, I PICTURED HER GETTING MAD
AT ME THE WAY YOU GOT MAD AT ME
AND I CHICKENED OUT,
SO I WROTE HER THAT NOTE.
WOULD YOU GIVE IT TO HER,
PLEASE?
YOU-YOU-YOU CAME TO SEE LILY?
YEAH, YEAH. WHY?
LILY'S DEAD.
SHE WHAT?
SHE'S DEAD.
ARE YOU SURE?
WELL, IF SHE ISN'T
CREMATING HER WAS BIG MISTAKE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HOW, HOW...? OH, MY GOD.
HOW-HOW LONG AGO?
17 YEARS AGO.
OH...
WHAT-WHAT ABOUT THE GIRLS?
WELL, URSULA IS A WAITRESS
AND SHE LIVES IN SOHO
AND PHOEBE...
IS ON THIS COUCH.
YEP. LIPSTICK AND A DAUGHTER.
BIG DAY FOR YOU, HUH?
PHOEBE, I-I-I, UM...
WHOOPS.
IT'S JUST...
I-I-I DON'T KNOW
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I JUST
CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
YOU'RE MY DAUGHTER.
YOU'RE SO PRETTY.
YES. WELL, THAT'S NEITHER
HERE NOR THERE.
SO, WOULD IT-WOULD IT
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER
IF I SAID THAT I WAS
VERY, VERY SORRY I LEFT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT YOU SAY.
IT'S NOT GOING
TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE ANYWAY
SO YOU CAN JUST GO.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
YOU KNOW, IN MY DEFENSE
I WAS A LOUSY FATHER.
THAT'S YOUR DEFENSE?
YES, IT IS.
I BURNED THE FORMULA
AND I PUT YOUR
DIAPERS ON BACKWARDS.
I MEAN, I MADE UP A SONG
TO SING YOU TO SLEEP
BUT THAT MADE YOU
CRY EVEN MORE.
YOU MAKE UP SONGS?
WELL, NO.
JUST THAT ONE.
IT WAS STUPID.
LET'S SEE.
HOW DID IT GO?
UM... YEAH. OKAY.
♪ SLEEPY GIRL, SLEEPY GIRL ♪
♪ WHY WON'T YOU
GO TO SLEEP? ♪
♪ SLEEPY GIRL,
SLEEPY GIRL ♪
♪ YOU'RE-YOU'RE-
YOU'RE KEEPING ME UP. ♪
WELL, YEAH.
I JUST...
I'M NOT VERY GOOD
AT THIS SO, UM...
WELL, I AM.
NOT YET, NO.
HEY, MAN, HOW'D
THE AUDITION GO?
ESTELLE SAID I DIDN'T GET IT.
WHAT? WHY?
JOEY, YOU WERE
SO READY FOR IT.
YEAH. I THOUGHT SO, TOO
BUT SHE SAID THE CASTING PEOPLE
HAD SOME PROBLEMS WITH ME.
WHAT KIND OF PROBLEMS?
WELL, TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
THEY, UH...
THEY HAD A PROBLEM WITH THE BAG.
OH, MY GOD.
NO...
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT WAS A STUPID PLAY, ANYWAY.
JOEY, I THINK IT'S TIME
TO GIVE UP THE BAG.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP THE BAG.
I DON'T HAVE TO GIVE UP THE BAG,
DO I, RACH?
YOU THINK I SHOULD GIVE UP
THE BAG.
WAIT, JOEY. I'M SORRY.
AS TERRIFIC AS I THINK
YOU ARE WITH IT...
OH, HEY.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
IF THE WORLD IS READY
FOR YOU AND YOUR BAG.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M HEARING THIS.
WAIT A MINUTE,
WAIT A MINUTE.
I'M NOT SAYING
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE A BAG.
I JUST... IT'S JUST THAT
THERE ARE OTHER BAGS, YOU KNOW
THAT ARE MAYBE A LITTLE LESS,
UM... CONTROVERSIAL.
YEAH. UM, THEY'RE
CALLED WALLETS.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]